newsnextbd.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy - cares for nothing but accuracy

This privacy policy explains our policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure and transfer of your information by [newsnextbd.com](http://newsnextbd.com/)  and/or its subsidiary(ies) and/or affiliate(s) (collectively referred to as the “[newsnextbd.com](http://newsnextbd.com/)”), which operates various websites and other services including but not limited to delivery of information and content via any mobile or internet connected device or otherwise (collectively the “Services”). This privacy policy forms part and parcel of the Terms of Use for the Services. Capitalized terms which have been used here but are undefined shall have the same meaning as attributed to them in the Terms of Use.

As we update, improve and expand the Services, this policy may change, so please refer back to it periodically. By accessing the [newsnextbd.com](http://newsnextbd.com/) website or this Application or otherwise using the Services, you consent to collection, storage, and use of the personal information you provide (including any changes thereto as provided by you) for any of the services that we offer.

[newsnextbd.com](http://newsnextbd.com/)  respects the privacy of the users of the Services and is committed to reasonably protect it in all respects. The information about the user as collected by [newsnextbd.com](http://newsnextbd.com/)  is: (a) information supplied by users and (b) information automatically tracked while navigation (c) information collected from any other source (collectively referred to as Information).

**INFORMATION RECEIVED, COLLECTED AND STORED BY NEWSNEXTBD.COM**

**Registration data:**

When you register on the website, Application and for the Service, we ask that you provide basic contact Information such as your name, sex, age, address, pin code, contact number, occupation, interests and email address etc. When you register using your other accounts like on Facebook, Twitter, Gmail etc. we shall retrieve Information from such account to continue to interact with you and to continue providing the Services. **  
**

**Subscription or paid service data:**

When you chose any subscription or paid service, we or our payment gateway provider may collect your purchase, address or billing information, including your credit card number and expiration date etc. However when you order using an in-app purchase option, same are handled by such platform providers. The subscriptions or paid Services may be on auto renewal mode unless cancelled. If at any point you do not wish to auto-renew your subscription, you may cancel your subscription before the end of the subscription term. **  
**

**Voluntary information:**

We may collect additional information at other times, including but not limited to, when you provide feedback, change your content or email preferences, respond to a survey, or communicate with us.

**B. INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED/ TRACKED WHILE NAVIGATION**

**Cookies**

To improve the responsiveness of the “Application” for our users, we may use “cookies”, or similar electronic tools to collect information to assign each visitor a unique, random number as a User Identification (User ID) to understand the user’s individual interests using the identified computer. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we will have no way of knowing who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply. A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. Our advertisers may also assign their own cookies to your browser (if you click on their ads), a process that we do not control. We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us via website, Application or Service though your computer/laptop/netbook or mobile/tablet/pad/handheld device etc.

**Log File Information**

We automatically collect limited information about your computer’s connection to the Internet, mobile number, including your IP address, when you visit our site, application or service. Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data — such as the pages you view. We automatically receive and log information from your browser, including your IP address, your computer’s name, your operating system, browser type and version, CPU speed, and connection speed. We may also collect log information from your device, including your location, IP address, your device’s name, device’s serial number or unique identification number (e.g.. UDiD on your iOS device), your device operating system, browser type and version, CPU speed, and connection speed etc.

## How to reach us

If you have any questions or comments about the [newsnextbd.com](http://newsnextbd.com/)s Privacy Policy please contact us via **[email](mailto:info@newsnextbd.com)** or write to us at:

**Development Media Ltd.  **

16/A(Level 4), Dilu Road, Eskaton,

Dhaka-1000, Bangladesh

Tel:          (880-2) 933 42 47

Mob:        (880-2) 1780 33 99 77

Fax:         (880-2) 933 42 48
